Perls Galleries
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Correspondence, 1937-1995, Series 1:; (Boxes 1-44, OV 81-83; 43.6 linear feet)
  - Berggruen, Heinz, 1943-1953 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Berggruen, John, 1978-1990 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Berggruen, John, 1968-1976 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Bergman, Edward A., 1956, 1973-1978 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Berkowitz, Rosalie, 1959-1970, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Berkowitz, Sidney, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - The Berkshire Museum, 1965-1966 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Berkson, Eleanor Lambert, 1945, 1959-1960, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Berle, Milton, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Berliner, A. L., 1955 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Berlinische Galerie im Gropiusbau, 1987-1989 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Bernays, Edward L., 1969-1982 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Bernoulli, Christoph, 1957-1969 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Bernoulli, Christoph, 1947-1956 (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Bernstein, Leonard S., 1959, 1965-1967, 1973-1980 (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Bernstein, Peter L., 1973-1990 (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Berry, Robert G., 1964-1968 (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Bertrand, E., 1957-1958 (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Betts, Hobart, 1960-1973, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Betty McLean Gallery, 1951-1953 (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Beyersdorf, Eric, 1974-1983 (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - Biddle, Cornelia, 1948, 1956, 1962-1972 (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - Biddle, George, 1949, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - Biddle, Mrs. Thomas, 1949-1953 (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - La Biennale di Venezia, 1949-1959, 1985-1987 (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - Birmingham Museum of Art, 1952-1958, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 76)
  - Black, Crawford A., 1965-1966 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Blake, Elizabeth B. (Guiberson), 1955-1961 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Blanchard, Carol, 1942-1952, 1969, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Blanchard, Peter P., 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Blaustein, Julian, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Bloch, George, 1972-1981 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Block, Leigh B., 1962-1978 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Block, Leigh B., 1948-1961 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Bloomingdale, Lyman G., 1939-1956, 1965, 1973-1978 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Bloomingdale's, 1966, 1983-1988 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Bluestein, Allan, 1968-1981 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Bluestein, Allan, 1966-1967 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Bluestein, Allan, 1963-1965 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Blum, Peter R., 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Blutman, Harry Austin, 1946, 1953-1960 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Board of Education of the City of New York, 1949-1951 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Boehm, Frank, 1973-1978 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Boël, René (Count), 1944, 1964, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Boesky, Ivan F., 1977-1979 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Bogart Gallery, 1974-1982 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Boghici, Jean, 1983-1989 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Bollag, Max B., 1952-1955 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Bondanini, Magy, 1952-1956 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Bonner, Lily, 1942-1955 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Bonniers, 1950-1957 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Boos, Frank H., 1938-1946 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Borenstein, Sam, 1945-1946, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Borman, Burton, 1968-1971 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Boston Book and Art Shop, Inc., 1952-1955 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Boston Public Library, 1945-1946, 1955-1957 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Boston Truck Co., Inc., 1962-1974 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Boulton, Schroeder, 1946, 1953-1956, 1963-1965 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Boustedt, Bo, 1973-1976 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Braasch, Theodor, 1944-1946 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Braasch, Theodor, 1943 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Bradley, Peter, 1965-1972 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Bragaline, Edward A., 1944-1962, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Bragno, Edward, 1951-1954 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Brandeis University, 1960-1967, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Brandt, Alan E., 1947-1984 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Brandt, Damon, 1980-1995 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Brandt, Paul, 1952-1958 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Braque, Georges, 1948, 1955-1956 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Brenman, Margaret, 1947-1948 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Brewster Gallery, 1972-1978, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Bricke, Ronald, 1970-1975 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Briest, Francis, 1978, 1984, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Briggs, Austin, 1958-1960, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Bright, David E., 1958-1965 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Brodie, Julian, 1937-1946, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Brody, Mrs. Sidney F., 1953-1955, 1965-1980 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Bronfman, Edward E., 1967-1973 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Bronfman, Peter F., 1971-1992 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Bronfman, Peter F., 1966-1970 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - The Brooklyn Museum, 1974-1989 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - The Brooklyn Museum, 1943-1973 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Brook Street Gallery, 1971-1981 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Brook Street Gallery, 1965-1970 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Brooks Memorial Art Gallery, 1943, 1965-1969, 1985-1986, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Brown, Mrs. Lathrop, 1940-1942, 1948, 1958, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Brown, Margaret, 1947-1948 (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Brown University, 1964-1965, 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Brown, William T., 1940-1947 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Buchholz Gallery, 1940-1951, (see also Curt Valentin Gallery) (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Budd Management Corp., 1943-1954 (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Budden, Alexander W., 1972-1982 (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - Burke, Harry F., 1946-1947 (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - Burke, Harry F., 1944-1945 (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - The Burlington Magazine Publications, Ltd., 1958-1973 (Box 5, Folder 69)
  - Burton, Irving F., 1961-1968 (Box 5, Folder 70)
  - Butler, John, 1949-1954 (Box 5, Folder 71)
  - Butler, Morgan R., Jr., 1954-1968 (Box 5, Folder 72)
  - Butler, Morgan R., Jr., 1943-1953 (Box 5, Folder 73)
  - Butterfield & Butterfield, 1989-1991 (Box 5, Folder 74)
  - Byck Gallery, 1972-1979 (Box 5, Folder 75)
  - Miscellaneous B, circa 1937-1995, (44 folders) (Box 6, Folder 1-44)
  - Cafritz, Calvin, 1962-1966 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Cafritz General Insurance Underwriters, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Cafritz, Gwendolyn, 1951-1952, 1964-1966 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Cain, Walter O., 1969-1976 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Caixa de Pensions, Centre Cultural, 1982-1983 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Calder, Alexander, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Calder Project: Albany, NY, Triangles and Arches, 1966-1975 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Calder Project: American Airlines, Red, Black, and Blue, 1967-1970 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Calder Project: Grand Rapids, MI, La Grande Vitesse, 1968-1969, (2 folders) (Box 6, Folder 53-54)
  - Calder Project: Grand Rapids, MI, La Grande Vitesse, 1969, (4 folders) (Box 7, Folder 1-4)
  - Calder Project: Hartford, CT, Stegosaurus, 1973-1975 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Calder Project: Hartford, CT, Stegosaurus, 1971-1972, (see also OV 81; OV 82) (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - California Palace of the Legion of Honor, 1945-1951 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Callery, Méric, 1939-1941 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Calnan, Philippa, 1961-1967 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Campbell, Arthur Bradley, 1943-1948 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Campbell, W. E., 1953-1954, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Campbell, W. E., 1951-1952 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Campbell, W. E., 1950 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Campbell, W. E., 1949 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Campigli, Massimo, 1956-1958 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Canaday, John, 1965-1985, (see also Box 80) (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Canadian Corporation for the 1967 World Exhibition, 1965-1966 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Cane, Martin, Buisine & Cie, 1940-1948 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Canfield, Cass, 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Cantor, Joseph, 1954-1970 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Carlen, Robert, 1950-1951, 1965-1967 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Carnegie Institute, 1962-1979 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Carnegie Institute, 1949-1961 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Carnegie Institute, 1945-1948 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Carnegie Institute, 1941-1944 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Carpenter, Charles H., Jr., 1946-1947 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Carré, Louis, 1938-1947, 1957-1968 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Carreño, Mario, 1962, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Carreño, Mario, 1944-1957 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Carreño, Mario, 1943 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Carreño, Mario, 1941-1942 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Carroll, J. Roy, Jr., 1971-1974 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Cars and Car Maintenance Records, 1954-1970 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Carstairs, Carroll, 1937-1949 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Carter, Dolly Bright, 1972, 1982-1985 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Castermans, Colette, 1993-1994 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Castle, Irving, 1964-1973 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Castleton China, 1949-1952, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Catherwood, Cummins, 1971-1975 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Catherwood, Cummins, 1943-1954, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Centre Georges Pompidou: Musée National d'Art Moderne, 1983-1995 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Centre Georges Pompidou: Musée National d'Art Moderne, 1978-1982 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Centre Georges Pompidou: Musée National d'Art Moderne, 1961-1977 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Cerf, Bennett, 1945, 1950, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Ceroni, Ambrogio, 1962-1970 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Ceroni, Anna, 1980-1981, 1987, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Chagall, Ida Meyer, 1984-1994 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Chagall, Ida Meyer, 1980-1983 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Chagall, Ida Meyer, 1976-1979 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Chagall, Ida Meyer, 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Chagall, Ida Meyer, 1971-1973 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Chagall, Ida Meyer, 1967-1970 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Chagall, Ida Meyer, 1955-1966 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Chagall, Marc and Valentine (Vava), 1963-1971 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Chagall, Marc and Valentine (Vava), 1940, 1948, 1956-1962 (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Chaim Soutine Catalogue Raisonné, 1985-1995 (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Chaim Soutine Catalogue Raisonné Party, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Champagne-Urbana Art Association, 1942 (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - Chandler, William H., 1963-1967 (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - Chaplin, Charles C. G., 1963-1967 (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - Charities, 1940-1969, (3 folders) (Box 8, Folder 1-3)
  - Charles H. MacNider Museum, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Charles J. Slicklen Company, Inc., 1963-1971 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Charles Z. Offin Advertising, 1973-1978 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Charney, Nicolas H., 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Charrell, Ludwig, 1940-1947, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - The Chase Manhattan Bank, 1941, 1954-1974 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Chermayeff, Serge, 1966, 1976-1977 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Choate, Mrs. Whitney Bourne, 1950-1954 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - The Christian Science Monitor, 1938-1951, 1972, 1980-1989 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Christie's, 1982-1989 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Christie's, 1976-1981 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Christie's, 1971-1975 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Christie's, 1954-1970 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Christopherson, C. R., 1948-1949 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Chrysler, Walter P., Jr., 1941-1945, 1955-1958, 1966-1967 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Chrysler, Walter P., Jr., 1938-1939 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Cincinnati Art Museum, 1954-1966, 1973-1981 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Cincinnati Modern Art Society, 1942-1954 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - City Art Museum of St. Louis, 1952-1961, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - City Art Museum of St. Louis, 1940-1946 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - City of Nagoya, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - City of Philadelphia, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Clapp, Christopher, 1987-1993 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Clark, James H., 1966-1968 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Classen, Wolfgang, 1980-1981, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Clearwater Art Museum, 1941-1957 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Clendinin, Eve, 1943-1947 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - The Cleveland Museum of Art, 1978-1992 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - The Cleveland Museum of Art, 1967-1977 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - The Cleveland Museum of Art, 1938-1966 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Clifford, Inda and Bill, 1953-1955 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Clumeck, Jack R., 1967-1973, 1982-1988 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Coberly, Victoria N., 1971-1976 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Cocke, Duncan McRae, 1977-1989 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Cohen, Herbert G., 1969-1975 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Cohen, Jack C., 1966-1970, 1976-1979, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Cohen, Marion, 1951, 1958, 1966, 1976-1979 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Cohen, Richard M., 1979-1983 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Cohen, Saul Z., 1966-1978, 1987-1991 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Colby Junior College, 1944-1947 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Cole, James R., 1971, 1980-1982 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Coleman, David, 1947-1960 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Coleman, James Julian, Jr., 1969-1971 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Colin, Ralph F., 1972-1985 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Colin, Ralph F., 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Colin, Ralph F., 1950-1953, 1962-1968 (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Collins, Barney W., 1962-1963 (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Colorado Springs Fine Arts Center, 1945-1946 (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Colt, Patricia Crum, 1944-1950 (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - The Columbus Gallery of Fine Arts, 1956-1959, 1964-1975, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - The Columbus Gallery of Fine Arts, 1945-1952 (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Columbus Museum of Art, 1956-1961, 1979-1986 (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - Comité Professionnel des Galeries d'Art, 1967-1970 (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - Contemporary Arts Association, 1956-1968 (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - The Contemporary Arts Center, Cincinnati, 1970-1982 (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - Contemporary Sculpture Center, 1985-1993, (see also OV 81) (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - Contemporary Sculpture Center, 1983-1984 (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - Contemporary Sculpture Center, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - Contemporary Sculpture Center, 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - Contemporary Sculpture Center, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - Contemporary Sculpture Center, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 64)
  - Contemporary Sculpture Center, 1976-1977 (Box 8, Folder 65)
  - Cooper, Douglas, 1953-1975, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Cooper, Herman E., 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - The Corcoran Gallery of Art, 1960-1973 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - The Corcoran Gallery of Art, 1940, 1945-1958 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Council for Inter-American Cooperation, Inc., 1946-1947 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Council of National Defense, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Courthon, Pierre, 1957-1966, 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Courvoisier Galleries, 1937-1939 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Cowles, John, 1947, 1962, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Cramer, Gerald, 1958-1965 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Cranbrook Academy of Art, 1945-1952 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Cranbrook Institute of Science, 1949-1950 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Crane Kalman Gallery, 1978-1994 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Crane Kalman Gallery, 1951-1975 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Crosby, Caresse, 1943-1953 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Cue Magazine, 1938, 1947-1949, 1961, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Cukor, George, 1946 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Cummer Gallery of Art, 1962-1963 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Cummings, Nathan, 1952-1955, 1963-1969 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - The Currier Gallery of Art, 1969-1973 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Curry, Charles E., 1966, 1982-1985, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Curry, Peter D., 1961-1974 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Curry, Peter D., 1955-1960 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Curt Valentin Gallery, 1952-1955, (see also Buchholz Gallery) (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Customs Forms and Receipts, 1947-1987 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Czwiklitzer, Christoph, 1955-1963, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Miscellaneous C, circa 1937-1995, (23 folders) (Box 9, Folder 27-49)
  - Miscellanous C, circa 1937-1995, (8 folders) (Box 10, Folder 1-8)
  - D. Matt, Inc., 1954-1959 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - D. Matt, Inc., 1950-1953 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - D. Matt, Inc., 1946-1949 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - D. Miller Restorers, Inc., 1957, 1974-1979 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Dabney, Beatrice, 1964-1947 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Dahl, Hermann M., 1941-1946 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Dain/Schiff Inc., 1955-1975 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Dali, Salvador, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - The Dallas Museum for Contemporary Arts, 1958-1962 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Dallas Museum of Fine Arts, 1973-1986 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Dallas Museum of Fine Arts, 1963-1967 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Dallas Museum of Fine Arts, 1940-1945, 1951 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - The Dalton Schools, 1960-1967, 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Dalzell Hatfield Galleries, 1939-1945, 1952, 1961-1963 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Damase, Jacques, 1951-1952 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - The Daniel B. Grossman Galleries, 1983-1993 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Danto, Art, 1947-1948 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Danzas & Cie, 1951-1965 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - d'Arquian, Maurice, 1952-1956 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Daskovs, Michael, 1980-1985 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - d'Atri, Alberto G., 1951-1953 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Davenport Munipal Art Gallery, 1950-1951, 1958-1959, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Davidson, Jean, 1958-1962, 1968-1970, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Davis, Dwight F., 1938-1946, 1953 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Davis, Julius E., 1976-1977, 1983-1989 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Davlyn Gallery, 1979-1980, 1995, (see also Galleria Internazionale; Nahmad, Giuseppi) (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - The Dayton Art Institute, 1963-1969 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - The Dayton Art Institute, 1931, 1941-1943, 1951-1954 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Dayton, Bruce B., 1966-1971, 1978, 1986-1988, (see also Dayton's Gallery 12) (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Dayton, Bruce B., 1950, 1958, 1964-1965, (see also OV 81; OV 82; Dayton's Gallery 12) (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Dayton's Gallery 12, 1969-1970, (see also Dayton, Bruce) (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Dayton's Gallery 12, 1968, (see also Dayton, Bruce) (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Dayton's Gallery 12, 1967, (see also OV 81; OV 82; Dayton, Bruce) (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - de Almeida, Helio, 1965-1968, (see also de Almeida, Sergio and Helio) (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - de Almeida, Sergio and Helio, 1980, (see also de Almeida, Helio) (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - de Barros Gomes, Jayme, 1966-1968 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - de Broglie, Jeanne-Marie, 1967-1971, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - de Broglie, Jeanne-Marie, 1961-1966 (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - De Cordova Museum, 1958, 1964-1966, 1973-1977 (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - de Croissert, Ethel, 1967-1973 (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - de Groot, Adelaide Milton, 1949-1951, 1958-1963 (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - de Guébriant, Wanda, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - de Léché, Alain, 1957-1964 (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - de Ménil, Adelaide, 1989, (see also de Ménil, Jean and Dominique; de Ménil, Marie-Christophe) (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - de Ménil, Jean and Dominique, 1969-1982, (see also de Ménil, Adelaide; de Ménil, Marie-Christophe) (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - de Ménil, Jean and Dominique, 1954-1968, (see also de Ménil, Adelaide; de Ménil, Marie-Christophe) (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - de Ménil, Marie-Christophe, 1975-1981, (see also de Ménil, Adelaide; de Ménil, Jean and Dominique) (Box 10, Folder 55)
  - de Vos, J. P., 1960, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - Demotte, Inc., 1938-1941 (Box 10, Folder 57)
  - Dennis, Robert F., 1983-1994 (Box 10, Folder 58)
  - Denver Art Museum, 1978-1982 (Box 10, Folder 59)
  - Denver Art Museum, 1958-1966 (Box 10, Folder 60)
  - Denver Art Museum, 1952-1957 (Box 10, Folder 61)
  - Denver Art Museum, 1942-1949 (Box 10, Folder 62)
  - Desjardins, Sophie, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 63)
  - Desjardins, Sophie, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 64)
  - Desjardins, Sophie, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 65)
  - Desjardins, Sophie, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 66)
  - Desjardins, Sophie, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 67)
  - Desjardins, Sophie, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 68)
  - Desjardins, Sophie, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 69)
  - Desjardins, Sophie, 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Desjardins, Sophie, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Desjardins, Sophie, 1971-1973 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Desjardins, Sophie, 1968-1970 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Des Moines Art Center, 1960, 1967-1973, 1980, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Deson-Zaks Gallery, 1973-1978 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - The Detroit Institute of Arts, 1961-1973, 1980-1987 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - The Detroit Institute of Arts, 1942-1951 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - The Detroit Institute of Arts, 1939-1941 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Dic Art Co., Ltd., 1988-1991 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Didisheim, Jacques, 1953-1955 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Division Water & Sewer Corp., 1954-1956 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Dobra, Alisan, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Dodell, Phillip, 1975-1978, 1984-1991 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Dodge, Joseph J., 1942-1946 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Donald Desky Associates, 1948-1949 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Donald Morris Gallery, 1970-1994 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Donald Morris Gallery, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Donald Morris Gallery, 1967-1968 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Donald Morris Gallery, 1965-1966 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Dorr, William, 1965-1966 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Douglas Gibbons & Co., Inc., 1947-1954 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Douglas, Kirk, 1967-1969 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Douglass, Dr. Frederick M., Jr., 1951-1956, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Dover Publications, Inc., 1964, 1970-1972 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - The Downtown Gallery, 1946-1955, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Drew, William B. F., 1965, 1975-1978 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Drexel Institute of Technology, 1964-1966 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Dreyfus, René, 1948, 1964-1980 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Driggs, Hamilton I., 1960-1961 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Du Long, Vaughan, 1947-1948 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - du Pont, Joanne, 1981-1982 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Dubourg, Jacques, 1951, 1964-1968 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Duchamp, Marcel, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Ducomm, Charles E., 1963-1967 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Dudensing, Richard, 1950-1956 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Dudensing, Valentine, 1937, 1943-1964 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Dufy, Jean, 1945-1946 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Dufy, Raoul, 1950-1951 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Dunkelman Gallery, 1966-1972 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Miscellanous D, circa 1937-1995, (30 folders); (see also OV 81) (Box 11, Folder 41-70)
  - E. J. Korvette, Inc., 1954, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - E. I. du Pont de Nemours & Co., 1947 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Eagle, Brian M., 1959-1960, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Echavarria, Maria, 1974-1978 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Edelson, Gilbert, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Edinburg, Dorothy B., 1952, 1961-1966, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Editions d'Art Albert Skira, 1954-1973, 1981-1985 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Edition "Cahiers d'Art", 1939-1966, 1981-1985 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Editions Publisol, 1970-1992 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Les Editions Réalités, 1972-1973 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - The Edmonton Art Gallery, 1981-1982 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Edward's Housewares, Inc., 1961-1981 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Edwards, Mrs. William C., Jr., 1966-1967 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Eichholz, Robert B., 1944-1947, 19853-1963, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Eisenbeiss, John, 1951-1952 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Eisenberg, Dorothy Coccagna, 1969-1978, 1987-1994 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Eisendieck, Suzanne, 1961-1976, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Eisendieck, Suzanne, 1954-1960 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Eisendieck, Suzanne, 1951-1953 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Eisendieck, Suzanne, 1949-1950 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Eisendieck, Suzanne, 1948, July-December (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Eisendieck, Suzanne, 1948, January-June (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Eisendieck, Suzanne, 1946-1947 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Eisendieck, Suzanne, 1938-1939 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Elgot Sales Corp., 1975-1987 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Elliott, George, 1945-1949 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Elliott, Osborn, 1978-1989 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Elsen, Albert, 1972-1974 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Emil, Allan D., 1953-1954, 1963-1966 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Encyclopaedia Britannica, 1945, 1959, 1968-1969, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Entwistle, Lance and Roberta, 1978-1994 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Epstein, Mr. and Mrs. Julius, 1962-1968, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Ernest O. Grossman, Bookbinder, 1950-1986 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Errera, Paul, 1966-1971, 1984-1994 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Esther Robles Gallery, 1977-1978 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Esquire, 1942-1944, 1969-1970 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Essellier, André-F., 1975, 1980, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Estudio Actual, 1968-1976 (Box 12, Folder 38)